unrealityshout.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy | Unreality Shout

Unrealitytv Limited are committed to ensuring that the privacy of those who use this web site is protected. This policy explains how we use the information we collect about you. If you have any queries concerning your personal information or any questions on our use of the information, please contact us at [info@unrealitytv.co.uk](mailto:info@unrealitytv.co.uk). 

When you register with us, we will need certain information from you to enable us to provide our services. You will be required to provide information about you and/or your business such as names and addresses used, contact details, and other basic information. In addition, we may collect other information from you in the course of your use of the web site or your submission of comments and/or requests to us. 

The personal information collected is used to enable us to provide our services to you, and will be stored on a secure server which is password protected. We may, as appropriate, use the personal information to improve our marketing, for administration and to provide our services. 

The infrastructure of the internet is global. It is not possible to predict the routes that information sent over the internet will take. Therefore, the information you provide from a source within the European Economic Area may be transmitted via a route that takes it outside that Area as it passes between you and us. 

By using this web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information in the manner set out above. If we change or modify our privacy policy, we shall post these changes on this page. 

0 Comments
